数学推导出来的
The math is all there.
- 这不可能  - 有可能的
- It's not real.  - Yes, it is.
好吧... 看 从科学角度来说
Yeah... uh, look. It is scientifically impossible
一个人不可能推倒一头牛
for a person to tip a cow.
哪怕你熊腰虎背的
Even you, with your stocky build
也没法做到
and lumberjack shoulders, you couldn't do it.
太残忍了 你干嘛要推倒一头牛?
It's horrible. Why would you push a cow over?
它们是神圣的
They're sacred.
够了
Oh, stop it.
我看你不也吃了上百万个汉堡嘛
I've seen you eat, like, a million hamburgers.
嘿 神圣的动物也可以很好吃啊
Hey, an animal can be both sacred and delicious.
听着 我说了我就这么干过 好吗?
Look, I'm telling you I've done it, okay?
我记得很清楚那头牛站着
I clearly remember the cow standing up
然后就被我推倒了
and then the cow on its side.
你当时喝醉了吗?
Were you drunk?
我当时在内达华州 只有16岁 你说呢?
I was 16 in Nebraska. What do you think?
我觉得你才是倒地的那个
I think you're the one who fell over.
这也就解释了为什么我看天空也倒下了
That would explain why the sky was also on its side.
嘿
Hey.
Howard 你说推倒一头牛: 是真是假?
Howard. Cow tipping: real or not?
嗯 我觉得... 是假的
Mmm. I'm gonna say... not.
因为我在我妈打呼噜时
That's just based on me trying to roll
也推不动她
my mom over when she's snoring.
说到那个胖女人
Speaking of that big side of beef,
她邀请你们大家感恩节去她家
uh, she's invited all of you to Thanksgiving at her house.
要知道 我听说没有理由地
You know, I've been told that a bald refusal
拒绝邀请很不友好 所以我必须
of an invitation is rude and one must instead
说一个借口以示礼貌...
offer up a polite excuse, so...
我很想去 但不幸的是
I'd love to go, but, unfortunately,
那听上去太糟了
that sounds awful.
来吧 会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun.
事实上 我们会在这里过感恩节
Uh, we were actually gonna do it here.
求你们了 因为Bernadette的妈妈出远门了
Please? Bernadette's bringing her dad
所以她要把爸爸接过来
'cause her mom's out of town,
我跟老头子什么共同语言都没有
and I never have anything to say to that guy.
既然你这么说了 我挺想去的
Oh, since you put it that way, I'd love to go,
但那听上去更糟糕了
but that sounds even more awful.
其实能让Sheldon抱怨别人的厨艺
It'd actually be nice to not hear
而不是我的 这挺好
Sheldon complain about my cooking all day.
你... 不好意思
Yo... uh, excuse me,
但每年你都会做一顿糟糕的饭菜
but every year you prepare a terrible meal
每次我都会批评一番
and every year I criticize it.
我们的传统在你看来就毫无意义吗?
Do our traditions mean nothing to you?
- 我想去  - 我也是
- I want to go.  - Yeah, me, too.
- 算我一个  - Sheldon
- I'm in.  - Sheldon.
好吧 我去
Ugh, fine, I'll go.
但如果她做的菜很好吃 那感恩节就毁了
But if her food is delicious, Thanksgiving is ruined,
到时候都赖你
and it's on you.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季第九集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Julie wanna307 碉堡千 初见
校对：uu要坚持!
我们真的得去Wolowitz夫人家吗?
Do we really have to go to Mrs. Wolowitz's house?
是的
We do.
我希望你能老老实实的
And I expect you to be on your best behavior.
现在我知道非洲黑奴的心情了
Now I know how the African slaves felt.
被迫离开家园 被白人奴役 做苦力活
Being dragged from their homes to labor under the yoke of the white man.
你真的要把去Wolowitz妈妈家吃感恩节晚餐这事
Are you honestly comparing Thanksgiving dinner at Wolowitz's mom's
跟人类史上最悲惨的惨剧之一比较吗?
with one of the greatest tragedies in the history of mankind?
是的
Yes.
Sheldon 其实去哪儿过感恩节都很开心的 我上次去拉斯维加斯就是
Sheldon, you can have a nice Thanksgiving anywhere. I spent one in Vegas.
你去过?
You did?
当然 那还是我跟Zack在一起的时候
Yeah, back when I was dating Zack.
Zack其实比我想象的更有趣
Zack was actually more fun than I thought.
我们去赌博 去了某个廉价的婚礼教堂
We gambled, we went to one of those cheesy wedding chapels,
还吃了顿可口的火鸡大餐
we had a really good turkey dinner.
这有点奇怪 我们当时毕竟是在脱衣舞厅呢
which was surprising, since we were at a strip club.
等下 你去了教堂?
Wait, you went to a chape?
是啊 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
我们办了一场假婚礼
We had one of those silly fake weddings.
呃 Penny...
Penny...
你知道那是真的吧?
you know those are real, right?
才不是 那是闹着玩的
No, they're not.
不 是真的
Yeah, they are.
不是啊
No, they're not.
就是真的
Yeah, they are.
- 他说得对  - 婚礼是真的
- He's right.  - They're real.
但是... 看起来不像啊
But it... didn't seem real.
我来问你
Let me ask you a question.
你当时有没有觉得 拉斯维加斯是倒着的?
At any point, was Las Vegas on its side?
嗨 老爸
Hi, Dad.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, honey.
哦 你还给大家买了啤酒
Oh, you brought beer for everybody.
呃 好吧 是给大家买的
Uh, okay, yeah, it's for everybody.
我其实真的只想安安静静地待在家里
I really just wanted to have a nice, quiet day at home
看看球赛
and watch the game.
你在这里也可以安安静静地看球赛啊
You can have a quiet day and watch the game here.
Howard 这药不管用!
Howard, the medicine's not working!
你只管吃就好了
You just took it.
至少让它进到你胃里!
At least let it reach your first stomach!
嗨 Mike
Hey, Mike.
我帮你拿吧
Let me help you out, there.
谢了 你妈妈怎么了?
Thanks. What's wrong with your mom?
哦 她痛风又发作了
Oh, her gout's flaring up.
这就证明一天一个苹果派可没法保持健康
Turns out an apple pie a day does not keep the doctor away.
我的小脚趾怎么会这么疼?
How can one little toe hurt so bad?
大概是被你全身的重量压的!
Maybe because that little piggy is being crushed by the barn!
她应该很快就会安静下来
She should quiet down soon.
我给她的止痛药都能让牛... 呃她倒了
I gave her enough pain meds to choke a... well, her.
我们一起做饭吧
I guess we're gonna have to do all the cooking.
我倒有个主意
I have a better idea.
你想都别想
If you think you're gonna make me
让我一个人做饭
do all this by myself, you're crazy.
我是打算让Raj一个人做饭的
I was gonna make Raj do it all by himself.
哦 确实是个好主意
Oh, well, that's a great idea.
车这么少 一路畅通啊
No traffic, we're sailing.
是啊
Yes.
就像在船上一样
Like we're on a ship.
从非洲开到美洲的船上
Coming from Africa to America.
Sheldon 这样做不好
Sheldon, that's completely inappropriate.
别总把自己比作奴隶
You can't keep comparing yourself to a slave.
遵命 Amy小姐
Yes, Miss Amy.
真不敢相信你和那个白痴结婚了
I can't believe you're married to that idiot.
呃 你能不能不说了? 我们是闹着玩的
Ugh, would you stop? We just did it as a goof.
不管是不是闹着玩的 你都已经结婚了!
Well, a goof or not, you're actually married.
你得想办法解决这件事
You need to get this taken care of.
我会的 你干嘛这么纠结这件事?
I will. Why are you making this such a big deal?
哦 哦 我知道原因
Oh, oh, oh, I have a reason.
没准是因为你同意嫁给Zack
It could be because you said yes to marrying Zack,
可是每次Leonard求婚的时候
but every time Leonard's proposed,
你都坚决反对
he's gotten a resounding no.
真的 我真的是这么想的
Yeah, that's just off the top of my head.
我要怎么办?
So how do I undo this?
你最好能和他离婚
I'm hoping you can get an annulment.
就像从没发生过一样
It's just like it never happened.
好啊 我要做什么?
Great, well, what do I have to do?
这上面说你只能在以下情况下
It says here you can get an annulment
解除婚姻关系
if any of the following conditions are met.
"你是否无法过上幸福的婚姻生活?"
"Were you unable to consummate the marriage?"
Penny? 还是看一下条吧
Penny? Next.
"有没有任何证据能证明婚姻关系中存在
"Is there any evidence of fraud, bigamy,
欺骗 重婚 或缺乏了解?"
want of understanding?"
"缺乏了解?"
"Want of understanding?"
那是什么意思?
What does that even mean?
叮咚 就这条了
Ding, ding, ding. We have a winner.
谢谢你今天来帮忙
Thanks for saving the day.
不用客气
Ah, no problem.
没有印度人(印第安人)做饭的感恩节
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
不叫感恩节
without an Indian providing the food.
你妈把黄油罐头放哪?
Uh, now, where does your mom keep the Crisco?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
可能在她脸上的那坨肉里
Probably in a wad in her cheek.
我在这帮Raj 你为什么不去陪陪我爸呢?
I'll help Raj in here. Why don't you go keep my dad company?
他不想让我陪他 我是个跟他女儿上床的
Oh, he doesn't want me in there. I'm the creepy little guy
猥琐矮子
who has sex with his daughter.
- 别傻了 他很爱你  - 是吗?
- Don't be silly, he loves you.  - Does he?
- 好吧 但他很关心你  - 真的吗?
- Okay, he cares about you a lot.  - Really?
我总给你收拾烂摊子 赶紧给我过去
I do crap for you all the time. Get out there.
你妻子跟孙子孙女在亚利桑那州是吧?
So your wife's in Arizona with the grandkids?
啊
Uh-huh.
其实 我妈也去过... 亚利桑那州
You know, my mom's been to... Arizona.
她骑着骡子去了大峡谷
She rode one of those mules down in the Grand Canyon.
长话短说 他们不得不毙了那头骡子
Long story short, they had to shoot it.
因为她很肥
'Cause she's so fat.
我去开门 你接着笑
I'll get the door while you finish laughing.
嗨 小伙伴们
Hey, guys.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
闻起来真香啊
It smells wonderful.
有没有人在厨房里干苦工啊?
Is anyone slaving away in the kitchen?
- 因为我也知道这滋味...  - Sheldon
- Because I, too, know...  - Sheldon.
给你 谢谢你让我们来吃饭
Here. Thank you for having us.
你什么情况?
What's with you?
她生我的气
Oh, she's mad at me
因为她刚发现她跟Zack结婚了
because she just found out she's married to Zack.
真的吗?
Really?
她之前交的那个笨蛋男朋友?
That dumb-ass she used to date?
实在太招笑了
That's hysterical.
我真不该为在车里开了这瓶酒而自责
I can't believe I felt bad for opening this in the car.
你需要帮忙吗?
You need any help?
需要 你能帮我把那个调味汁瓶够下来吗?
Uh, yeah, can you, uh, reach that, uh, gravy boat up there?
- 好  - 太棒了
- Uh, sure.  - Great.
终于有个人能够着了
That makes one of you.
好 我们在很短的时间内要做很多事
Okay, we have a lot to do and not much time to do it.
Bernadette 你负责玉米 调味汁和山药
Bernadette, you're on corn, gravy and yam detail.
Amy 你负责面包卷 越桔
Amy, you're on rolls, cranberries
还要保证Bernadette离棉花糖远远的
and making sure Bernadette stays away from the marshmallows.
没错 我看见你偷吃了
That's right, I see you.
好 如果你们有什么问题
Okay, if you have any questions,
我就在这脚打后脑勺地干活
I'll be over here basting my ass off.
集中精力是关键
Focus is key.
你们知道Penny跟Zack三年前结婚了吗?
Did you guys know Penny married Zack three years ago?
什么? 什么...?
What? Wha...?
你玩过橄榄球吗?
You ever play football?
在大学里玩过
A little in college.
你呢?
You?
没踢过
No.
但我在走廊里被撞过一次
But I did get tackled in the hallway once.
整个学校都雀跃了
The whole school cheered.
我找到了你跟Zack需要填的
Hey, I found the, uh, court papers
法律文件
that you and Zack need to fill out.
- 回家之后我就把它们打出来  - 行
- I'll print them when we get home.  - Fine.
然后我们就把这篇翻过去
And we can just put this whole thing behind us.
你够了没?
Are you done?
- 怎么了?  - 我知道 我搞砸了
- What?  - Look, I get it, I screwed up.
但我们这一天都要谈这个事吗?
Is this all we're gonna talk about the rest of the day?
你为什么跟我生气?
Why are you mad at me?
干了蠢事的那个人是你
You're the one that did the stupid thing.
- 我只是在挽救  - 啊!
- I'm just trying to fix it.  - Ugh!
我需要新鲜空气
I need some air.
但... Penny
Well... Penny.
虽然我一点也不了解女人
Now, I don't know the first thing about women,
但我绝对不会追出去
but I would not follow her.
好好看比赛
Listen the stretch.
我怎么成坏人了?
How am I the bad guy?
她是那个跟别人结婚的人 我是受害者
She's the one who married someone else. I'm the victim.
听起来Zack才是受害者 你在睡他媳妇呢
Sounds like Zack's the victim. You're sleeping with his wife.
我跟我的老太婆已经结婚35年了
I've kept my marriage together for 35 years.
所以我能插一句吗?
Can I weigh in here?
当然
Sure.
我想好好看比赛啊 闭嘴
I'm trying to watch the game. Shut up.
喔!
Oh!
你们这群人是怎么把首攻给搞砸的啊?
How do you not make a first down there?
他们想要冲出五人防守阵势
They passed against a nickel defense.
但是他们应该用离铲球策略才对
They should have run it off-tackle.
天呐 你是怎么知道这些的?
How the hell do you know that?
我爸爸喜欢橄榄球
My father loved football.
他过去经常逼我看比赛
He always made me watch it
然后他才允许我去做作业
before I was allowed to do my homework.
好了 这下你开心了
Well, you'll be happy
我已经跟Zack通过话了
to know I just spoke to Zack
他愿意在协议书上签字
and he's willing to sign the court papers.
他正在过来的路上
He's on his way here now.
- 等等 你把他请到这里来了?  - 是啊
- Wait, you invited him here?  - Yeah.
我准备要再插一句了
I'm getting ready to weigh in again.
过来
Come on.
你认为现在他们该怎么做?
What do you think they ought to do now?
我会让外接员快速斜角跑来应接传球员
I would throw a quick slant to a wideout,
因为防守方准备向传球员发动突然袭击
given that the defense is showing blitz.
喔 我可喜欢吃薄煎饼了 特别是蘸了酸奶的那种
Oh, I love a good blitz, especially with sour cream.
(blitz音似blintz 一种煎饼)
听懂没?
Get it?
因为这两个词听起来很像
'Cause it sounds like "blintz."
是不是有人说煎饼了?!
Did someone say "blintz"?!
我就是不明白
I just don't understand
为什么你要请他今天到这里来
why you invited him here today.
那是因为你不停地说这件事
Because you wouldn't shut up about it.
我给他打电话的时候 他没什么事可干
When I called him, he had nothing to do,
所以我就想啊 过来也挺...
so I just thought it would...
嗨 伙计们 我在这辛苦地准备大餐啊
Hey, guys, I'm trying to cook in here.
喔 不好意思 我们声音会小一点
Oh, sorry. We'll keep it down.
不 不 大声点
No, no, speak up.
我马上要用搅拌机了
I'm about to use the blender,
我怕听漏了什么
and I don't want to miss anything.
好吧 你可能要多准备一人份了
Well, you might have to cook for one more
因为她请了Zack过来
because she invited Zack.
- 不是吧?  - 喔!
- What?  - Ooh!
我的天啊 我的天啊
My, my.
故事的情节 就想我的肉汁一样 越发变成一团糊糊了
The plot, like my gravy, thickens.
我真不喜欢你妈妈的厕所
I don't care for your mother's bathroom.
不管我站在那个角度办事
There's not an angle to do one's business
都有一个小丑的塑像在盯着我看
without a clown figurine staring at you.
所以我坐着办事啊
That's why I sit.
啊 原来如此
Yeah, that's why.
你记得感恩节的那场
You remember the Thanksgiving game
在下雪的达拉斯举行的比赛吗?
when it snowed in Dallas?
那是1993年 Leon Lett在比赛的最后关头搞砸了
1993. Leon Lett blew the game in the final seconds
结果Dolphins赢得了胜利
and the Dolphins emerged victorious.
然后我终于能开始写微积分作业了
Then I finally got to do my calculus.
我那时候太生气了 都想把电视机给砸了
I was so pissed, I wanted to shoot my TV.
我爸也这么想
So was my dad.
然后他确实把电视机砸了
And then he did.
- 有没有人想要啤酒?  - 我
- Anyone need a beer?  - Yeah.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
那现在 你父亲还住在德州吗?
So, does your dad still live in Texas?
不了 他在我14岁的时候去世了
No. He died when I was 14.
真遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
我们那卖酒的人也是这么觉得的
So was the man who owned the local liquor store.
他哭的不行
He cried and cried.
给你
Here you go.
喔 谢谢
Oh, thanks.
所以 你父亲在你14岁的时候就去世了
So, if your dad died when you were 14,
你从来没有机会跟他好好喝一杯吧
you were never old enough to have a beer with the man.
没有
No, sir.
他确实想要在我的高中毕业典礼上跟我喝一杯
He did try to give me one for my high school graduation,
但是那个时候我只有11岁 我妈不让我喝酒
but I was 11 and my mom said no.
那么 你今天就跟我喝一杯吧
Well, you're having one with me.
好啊
All right.
敬你的父亲
To your dad.
我也没机会和我爸共饮啤酒
I never had a beer with my dad, either.
别捣乱 我们这儿正开心着呢
Do you mind? We're having a moment here.
我真不相信Penny嫁给Zack了
I can't believe Penny's married to Zack.
不知道看上那家伙哪点了
Wonder what she saw in that guy.
不知道
I don't know.
他很温柔 又高大 很帅气
He's sweet, he's tall, handsome.
肩膀宽阔 头发也不错
Broad shoulders, good hair.
那她看上Leonard哪点了呢
Hmm. Wonder what she sees in Leonard.
外面如何?
How's it going out there?
Sheldon和你爸爸很合得来 完全把我无视了
Sheldon and your dad are bonding and completely ignoring me.
我了解你此刻的想法
I know how you feel.
当Sheildon买了那台自动吸尘器 一个星期没理过我
Sheldon ignored me for a week when he got that Roomba vacuum.
我趁他不注意把那玩意弄坏了
I kick it when he's not looking.
他们在干嘛?
What are they doing?
喝着啤酒 看着球赛
They're drinking beer and watching football.
那你为啥不去加入他们呢?
So, why don't you do that with them?
他们不想我在那儿
They don't want me.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
Sheldon说他的父亲
Well, Sheldon started talking
已经不在人世
about how his dad isn't alive anymore,
然后他们在喝酒 然后我就
and they were toasting, and I tried
说我有多悲伤
to tell them about how sad I was
被我爸抛弃...
when my dad abandoned...
Zack来了!
Zack's here!
搅拌肉酱
Stir the gravy.
抱歉 我虽然很想继续听你说
Sorry. I really want to hear how sad you are.
等我5 哦 不 等我10分钟
I'll be back in like five, ten minutes.
真不好意思耽误你放假的日子过来
Sorry she made you come over here on a holiday.
没关系 反正我也没啥事
It's all right. I didn't have anything going on.
而且 Penny刚告诉我说我们结婚了
Plus, Penny told me we're married,
而且感恩节就是家人团聚的时候
and Thanksgiving's a time to be with family.
好吧 很好
Yeah, okay, great.
我们能不能赶快了结这事儿?
Can we just get this over with?
好吧 你们必须在这儿签字
Yeah, uh, you guys have to sign here and here.
星期一 就去离婚登记
On Monday, we'll file for the annulment,
这场"婚姻"就结束了
and this "marriage" will be over.
好
Okay.
我觉得我不太想签
I don't know if I want to sign it.
哦 哦 哦
Ooh. Ooh. Ooh.
为什么你不签字?
Why won't you sign it?
我想 如果我们离婚 对孩子很不好
I just think splitting up can be rough on kids.
我们没有孩子
We don't have any kids.
确定吗? 因为直到今早
Are you sure? 'Cause you didn't know
你才直到我们结婚
we were married until this morning.
好吧 Zack 别这样
Okay, look, Zack, come on.
咱都不认为那场婚礼是认真的
You know neither of us thought this was real.
主婚的可是个扮猫王的人啊
I mean, we were married by an Elvis impersonator.
当然是个扮演者
Of course it was an impersonator.
我们雇不起猫王啊
We could never afford a real Elvis.
你嫁他不嫁我?
You married him instead of me?
很明智
Good call.
签了它
Sign the papers.
等下 你知道吗?
Hang on. You know what?
你今天一直很刻薄
You have been a jerk about this all day.
每次你都这样... 每次当我搞砸了
You always do this... whenever I mess up,
你都大加嘲讽 让我更加不爽了
you're right there to make me feel even worse about it.
不是这样啊
That is not true.
是啊 我们本可以等到星期一
Yeah, we could've waited till Monday,
再签这玩意 这就很简单了啊
signed the papers, this all would have been over.
可是你请他过来的
You're the one who invited him here.
好吧 你又来了... 又在指责
Oh, there you go again... just another mistake
我的过错
you're throwing in my face.
这可不好 老兄
Not cool, bro.
我开始觉得
I'm starting to think
你并不适合和我老婆约会
you're not the kind of guy I want dating my wife.
好吧
Yeah, well,
她很快就不是你的老婆了
she's not gonna be your wife for long.
哦不 你快死了?
Oh, no. Are you dying?
快了 你快签吧
I'm about to. Sign the paper.
知道吗 "老婆好才是真的好"
Know what they say: "Happy wife, happy life."
我们开吃吧
Let's eat.
二 三 八 四 六
Two, three, eight, four, six.
不吐的话 这是我的极限了
That's all I can do without throwing up.
我可不这么想
That is not what I expected
你不是说你要把"圆周率"嗝一遍吗
when you said you were gonna burp "pie."
有人说有"馅饼"吃吗?!
Did somebody say "pie"?!
(馅饼和圆周率都读pie)
我分不清哪个更吓人
I don't know what's scarier
是那个浴室的小丑
the bathroom clowns
还是那个老女人
or the woman that put them there.
我只知道 车里只能塞进她一个人
All I know is you can only fit one of her in a car.
这就是她生出来的小丑
And there's the clown that came out of her.
我本来不愿意来的
I really didn't want to come here,
但我现在觉得
but this is shaping up to be
这是长久以来我过得最好的感恩节
one of the best Thanksgivings I've had in a long time.
我也是
Me, too.
嘿 Howie说你们俩嘲笑了他一天了!
Hey. Howie says you've been making fun of him all day!
你们快给他道歉
Now, both of you apologize
立刻马上!
right now!
她那么小只
She's so tiny.
发起脾气来真有意思
It's funny when she's mad.
好了 先生们
All right, mister, I think you owe
你们应该向Howard和Bernadette说声对不起
Howard and Bernadette an apology.
好吧 你说得对
Perhaps you're right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry for my behavior.
我喝高了
I've had alcohol, and it's caused me
所以做了出格的事情
to be inappropriate.
- 没关系  - 别放在心上
- It's okay.  - Don't worry about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
她很棒 是吧?
Ain't she great?
嗯
Mmm.
Sheldon 别这样
Sheldon.
给我们拿点酒来 怎么样?
Now, how's about you get us a couple of beers?
谢谢你做了这么好吃的食物
Thanks again for cooking.
是啊 很美味
Yeah, everything was delicious.
如果没有这两位女士的帮助
Well, I couldn't
我是做不出来这些美味的
have done it without my two favorite girls.
哦
Aw.
她们是玛莎·斯图尔特和瑞秋·雷(都是美食节目女主持)
Martha Stewart and Rachael Ray.
嘿 Sheldon 我们出去
Hey, Sheldon, what do you say we go outside
扔球玩怎么样?
and throw around the old pigskin?
(橄榄球的俚语 直译为猪皮)
这里是犹太家庭
This is a Jewish house.
他们没有猪皮的
I don't think they have pigskin.
有人说"猪皮"了?!
Did someone say "pigskin"?!
亲爱的 今天真是抱歉
Hey, honey, I'm sorry about today.
我答应你 下次如果我结婚了
And I promise, next time I get married,
肯定不是玩笑
it won't be a joke.
是为了爱情
It'll be for love.
或者为了钱
Or money.
我也有错
I'm sorry, too.
你没有
Don't be.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我是个不合格的丈夫
I was a terrible husband.
一直不在你身边
I was never around.
我知道我对你有点严厉
I know I'm hard on you,
但你不是最糟糕的女婿
but you're not the worst son-in-law in the world.
Mike 这是你对我说过最亲切的话了
Mike, that's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
我喝高了
Well, I'm drunk.
我吐在好多小丑身上了
I just vomited on a lot of clowns.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Julie wanna307 碉堡千 初见
校对：uu要坚持!